okay, so here comes Star Health Insurance
Company. Before this, let me give you information about
what kind of company it is and what work it does. Take a
look at it. It was
started in 2005 and the business of this company
and its name is Star Health
and Allied Insurance and
with almost sixteen percent market share, you will see this company which is appointed as the country's
leading
subscriber.
Subscribe to it right now and while doing
this work there, apart from this,
give its details. Tell me the complete details
of the IPO which is open. It will ask for pricing, lot size, issue
price.
Absolutely sir, it will remain open till today. You will be
able to apply for 870, 916.
Subscribe for 5250. So last year, there is
also an offer for sale of Rs 2,000 crores, where you are
giving exit option to existing investors. Along with this, we are seeing that a
lot of big investors have invested money, about Rs
3200 crores. Bigg Boss.
We know that the big investor of the market,
Rakesh Jhunjhunwala is associated with the company,
so it is a good company.  Director and all the
special guests are present in the program, the
MD of the company Dr. Prakash is present in the program
and I would like to introduce you to him,
you have done your
Bachelor's degree in Medicine and Surgery from Bharathidasan University, Dehradun, Tamil Nadu,
after that you have done your Master's degree in Medicine and Surgery from Doctor MGR College,
Dhaka Medical University, and
you have worked for a long time in Tamil Nadu as a gentleman,
one more special
guest is joining us in the program, he is
Mr. Anand Roy, he is also an actor and massage less, he is
always in character,
Rohit has done
B.Com from Madras University, he has done his post graduation diploma from International Management
Institute, New Delhi, he has
deep experience of more than 21 years in the insurance industry,
from both sides,
you always have difficulty in understanding and speaking Hindi, sir, I will
ask you questions in Hindi, if you don't understand,
Azami and
reduction in English, you can answer and that you can
easily write Hindi English mix like Arf
tables, please such answer complaint, first
question,
Prakash 20 crores which you can use  We are here to
subscribe and before that
tell the business model of the company and
tomorrow morning two thousand crore right now like him who want to send
for capital
infusion to maintain solvent seal then
our company but except doing company
which state into to 6 journey standalone
health insurance company deposit
that now these general insurance companies were doing
farmer and motor health tips to get into the
sanction width no dongri health
insurance fund in health insurance designer
products want price 50ml today at all
people in India can buy this code officer
contract panel and own hospital all over India
where will approach towards us and
hospital idea in this endeavor to last
for both plus doctors
available and process in decline soviet
design also product and deliver services
depression voice recorder version then
standalone health insurance company today
chief one trust and confidence of rs.2 feel
and more than phase plus 28 cent agents to
work with us chod meanwhile
studio star health insurance is wait
for you for  The question ok thank you thank
you so much Mishra Anand and Lu March
2018 2020 the company was profitable in March so a
little bit
and did
not subscribe
again the company will be profitable soon
so what is the
need thank you very much for wins see the
question you asked is a very correct question
because the company
was profitable in March Twenty20 not only in March Twenty20 if
you set an alarm for the 5 years before that
you will see that the company is
continuously profitable and it is a
profitable company but in
May Twenty21 as everyone knows there has been a
huge VAT interest in the entire industrial and
shipping industry especially and
in the rest of the insurance industry as well so because of that
Bihar to Chapter note of but claims and because of which our
company has to be some nolo
from interviewer 2021 apart from this the company made
two more changes in its accounting
practices one we have made about 16 inches which is
very urgent and we are making it a  We proved it
and had to increase the promise a little bit.
Our regulations like oil
are incomplete and apart from that, there is an accounting
practice, but now we can do 50% of our
vitamins or
use our UP and questions on a 15065 basis.
So we changed that accounting practice
to 12365. For that also we had to
create a lot of provisioning results. By
combining all these things, the company was launched a little bit in Badmaash Twenty-One
and it was afraid of maximum system accounting
practices due to the situation and there was a little bit of
knowledge due to quality. But this year, the
current financial year - Tamil
Sector-21, there is a difficulty for Twenty-Two that those who are
second, stupid but very difficult
online, industry leaders, which no one had ever
participated so much, so there are
difficult questions in the first four months,
for that our
pension research for the first half is writing the launch in it. But the
good thing is that for the last two months and
even this month, we are seeing that the
traffic in Dubai is decreasing like
Tweets are decreasing in the entire population, our
company schemes are also decreasing, so we
hope that this year there will be a little interest in
muting, but next year again
we will be able to work in a profitable manner and
we are very confident that the company which was
showing profit in the last 5 years, will continue to do
profitable business in the future as well. Okay, so
let's stop this, that there has been a
little decline in profitability due to the comments, even now the
measurement will be correct and there will be
improvement again, celery will remain and tell me
those investors who are
leaving with your question, the rest of the investors are
also selling ads in offer for sale and
Mushaira 250 crore dad was published, what
is the weather in the investors learning from the
fifth month after the people Vaseline and
private equity investors and went from
times over and those people who have
invested long back
1566 back Mr. Rakesh Ranjan vs John Cena
298 Strong Believer Mandsaur  Health insurance
brand Hamari Operation Samay Government but
oil strongly advocates of war and he
is not deleting in your feet step continues to hold all this
chant and his
supporters and he is the well clear
videeshwar paayenge iske computers se 19th
friends people who are selling a year of
immediate relief for several years from
history private equity investments
inside visitors for more than 50 and 100 m to
mr unnao 1000 percent
questions are in people's mind
in march 2017 your
in december 2004
pension of only 909080 has been launched a little weak it had happened
in these six months also so then what is the
reason that you are giving water at double the price
and that too to the people to whom you have
given stock in your professional allotment
there is also a bridge in this IPO so people
think why should we buy at double the price
when there is less gift  It is not a shampoo,
what do you have to say on this,
daughter, you will have to look at it on full contact, those who have
children, as Doctor
Prakash told, the people whose allotment
demand was given in December, are
not selling sex cess,
rugs, on this number we had tried it out
where American tastes were around Rs 2600 crore
and this time our
pricing, valuation has been done on the
basis of complete fundamental analysis,
our investment bankers have checked it by
talking to many Indian and global investors that they have defeated this price
and the fundamentals of the company, the
market
face of the company, the growth potential of the industry,
this company has full
confidence that it will be able to capture the growth
because as you told
in your introduction, we have a market share of more than 15 crore
and our retail business is
more than 30 percent of the market,
all the companies including public sector
companies and the rest of the private companies, so that
this company and its
growth of insurance and the
role of this work in the opposition
They have priced it considering the future potential
and I am hopeful that the public will feel
confident that this is a great company
and should invest in it. Okay, add
Prakash or once again the
risk of friends is increasing all over the world and there is a
little tension that friends
may come, new viral rock, Twitter, new
media,
last chapter fifth of equal has a lot of fans.
If the risk
increases again like this, then can it have any impact on the company's friendship offer?
CEO Micron Double Newton seen slow
viral disease which comes only and male
mutation in Bengali, you and 100 people are not surprised to hear them in a
profit, new
trends like to make another thing about me right now
in India, symptoms experienced mode 9
people and vaccine and definition of pain
in a very big too and Indian hospitals,
doctors and now will bring to front mill
west will not bill Prem Secretary
Vidhi number of an object suicide in the
hospital but  Subsequently returned from New Delhi
of clarity on how to creative
patient infected with corona Middle East
barriers and how to and business man power how to
make in its place all testing
Vinod hospital industry insurance
industry everyone will prevent and
reduce the impact of
birds want your system and picture and
dropping this is the impact of dishonor PM
will lead to force much SH developed best
video recording software
185 and Modi are very strong in amlo
and research bill come up with a new way are what is
going to be the impact of this
is not give more cases everyone
verification option circulation level and
oxygen supply for patients suffering from
disease or only at least
20 and paracetamol is subscribed for people
and 500 companies in hospital today people will try to avoid you need not be foundish continue to be
identified in the
dwarf planet among the public
not obscene alarm to
one side so doctors  Yes gentleman, you are
not from Uttar Pradesh, only from the insurance company, so
who knows better than you, so you definitely
share your experience, a doctor is visarjan
must be coming, very handy question Bihar flu
handed overall friend mixed situation,
thank you very much for
talking to us and best wishes for you, we
hope that the way
you will do as we need,
thank you, thank you.